<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 12:30:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Insights on Youtube Live</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights/
            </link>
            <description>
                Yesterday, Emmanuel Bernard and I kicked off Quarkus Insights #0: Inception. All based on this tweet where ~76% was up for us doing "something" in video/podcast&#8217;y style. It is going to be recorded live as part of our existing QuarkusIO channel. To be notified when new shows are planned and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Mocking CDI beans in Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mocking/
            </link>
            <description>
                Testing Quarkus applications has been an important part of the Quarkus Developer Joy, which is why @QuarkusTest for testing JVM applications and @NativeTest for black-box testing of the native images have been part of Quarkus since the first release. A recurring request however amongst our community members has been to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mocking/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for Eclipse 4.15.0.Final release !</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/eclipse-quarkus-tools-4.15.0.Final/
            </link>
            <description>
                In a previous post, we announced the first version of Quarkus Tools for Eclipse. We&#8217;re now announcing a new version for Quarkus Tools for Eclipse, including better support for Eclipse Microprofile, Java 11 and enhancements to the wizard. Language support for Kubernetes, Openshift, S2i and Docker properties There is now...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/eclipse-quarkus-tools-4.15.0.Final/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Learn how to do Mutual TLS in Quarkus apps</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-mutual-tls/
            </link>
            <description>
                In this entry, we explore how to set mutual TLS encryption between two Quarkus applications manually. Both on bare metal and Kubernetes. What is Mutual TLS Authentication? Mutual TLS authentication or two way authentication is an extension of Transport Layer Security (or “TLS”), and it ensures that traffic between the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-mutual-tls/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.4 released - Command mode, HTTP 2, New FaaS framework, Mocking...</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-4-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Here comes the time of the month when you get your new Quarkus release: 1.4.1.Final is here. No 1.4.0.Final, we had to skip it. This version is packed with very nice features and includes tons of improvements and bugfixes: Command mode HTTP/2 New FaaS framework called Funqy Improvements around mocking...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-4-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Free Quarkus Sessions at Red Hat Summit</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-summit-2020/
            </link>
            <description>
                In case you haven&#8217;t heard, next week&#8217;s Red Hat Summit is an online "Virtual Experience" with all of its content freely available (with registration)! Here is a handy session guide for the Keynote, Technical Sessions, and Quarkus in Production Customer Sessions, where Quarkus is either covered or is the central...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-summit-2020/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>A IO thread and a worker thread walk into a bar: a microbenchmark story</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/io-thread-benchmark/
            </link>
            <description>
                A competitor recently published a microbenchmark comparing the performance of their stack to Quarkus. The Quarkus team feels this microbenchmark shouldn’t be taken at face value because it wasn’t making a like-to-like comparison leading to incorrect conclusions. Both of the two frameworks under comparison support reactive processing. Reactive processing enables...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/io-thread-benchmark/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code - 1.4.0 release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.4.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.4.0 has been released on the VS Code Marketplace. vscode-quarkus 1.4.0 fixes several bugs, including some performance issues, but the highlights of this release revolve around bringing support for multiple MicroProfile modules (Fault Tolerance, Health, LRA, Metrics, Open API, Open Tracing, Rest Client), in...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.4.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Why did Payair Technologies switch to Quarkus?</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-did-payair-technologies-switch-to-quarkus/
            </link>
            <description>
                Developing cloud-ready solutions has become an industry standard, especially in the enterprise world. Sooner or later your application has to face the problem of poor horizontal scalability or high memory usage and we all know it is better to be prepared. We understand this at Payair as well. When we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-did-payair-technologies-switch-to-quarkus/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.3.2.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released 1.3.2.Final today with bugfixes and documentation improvements. This is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.3.0.Final or 1.3.1.Final. It is a very recommended upgrade if you are using Hibernate ORM. What&#8217;s new? Bugfixes We fixed a couple of regressions introduced recently in the Hibernate ORM extension. We...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-2-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
