<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 08:26:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #7</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-7/
            </link>
            <description>
                Welcome to Quarkus Newletter #7, this time with a record number of links to Quarkus related articles/videos/etc. all found online for you to explore. For the news below - give it a read and if you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for future Quarkus Newsletter...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-7/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>gRPC with Quarkus!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-grpc/
            </link>
            <description>
                In Quarkus 1.5, we shipped the first version of the gRPC Quarkus extension. If you are not familiar with gRPC, it&#8217;s a highly efficient Remote Procedure Call mechanism relying on HTTP/2 and Protobuf. You can implement and consume gRPC services from any language such as Go, JavaScript, Python, and Java....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-grpc/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.0.0 release !</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.0.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.0.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release brings enhanced code completion and syntax validation for application.properties and better support for Microprofile in Java files. It is not based anymore on the LSP Support plugin in order to increase stability. In order...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.0.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Supersonic Subatomic GraphQL</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/supersonic-subatomic-graphql/
            </link>
            <description>
                MicroProfile GraphQL is now included in the just released version 1.5.0 of Quarkus. What is GraphQL? "GraphQL is an open-source data query and manipulation language for APIs, and a runtime for fulfilling queries with existing data. GraphQL interprets strings from the client, and returns data in an understandable, predictable, pre-defined...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/supersonic-subatomic-graphql/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.5.2.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.5.2.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.5.0.Final or 1.5.1.Final. What&#8217;s new? We fixed two important regressions: The IDE launcher is back on track. In 1.5, we tweaked how the Hibernate ORM Panache enhancement works and that might...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-2-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Global Hackathon</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-hackathon-announcement/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Quarkus community is excited to announce the Supersonic, Subatomic Java Hackathon for developers to create Kubernetes-native applications for a chance to win $30,000 in prizes. This hackathon is a great opportunity to learn about the future of cloud-native Java development and showcase your coding skills. The Quarkus community and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-hackathon-announcement/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.5.1.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.5.1.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.5.0.Final. What&#8217;s new? You can get the full changelog of 1.5.1.Final on GitHub. Come Join Us We value your feedback a lot so please report bugs, ask for improvements&#8230;&#8203; Let&#8217;s build...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Insights #4 and #5: JHipster and Quarkify</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-4-5/
            </link>
            <description>
                We got two more Quarkus insights up and ready. #4 about JHipster for Quarkus with Daniel Petisme and #5 on Quarkify with Dmitry Chaban. Next Episode(s) On Tuesday June 9th 05:00 EST / 11:00 CEST / 14:30 IST we will do Quarkus Insights #6: GraalVM and Mandrel with Andrew Dinn....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-4-5/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.5 released - fast-jar packaging format, Picocli, gRPC, GraphQL and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus 1.5.0.Final is finally here with all sorts of bells and whistles: New fast-jar packaging format Picocli extension gRPC extension Eclipse MicroProfile GraphQL extension Amazon Services extensions Hibernate ORM REST Data with Panache extension Spring Cache compatibility layer It also includes a lot of bugfixes and small improvements all over...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Insights #3: Hibernate with Panache</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                Monday we did Quarkus Insights episode #3: Hibernate Panache with Stéphane through what Panache is, why it is awesome and how you get the most out of it. Podcast feed If you prefer to listen to these in podcast format they are now available from Apple Podcasts and should shouw...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-3/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
