<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 15:13:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Insights #2: quarkus:dev and Command mode</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-2/
            </link>
            <description>
                This week Quarkus Insights #2 was live and recorded with Stuart showing command mode and talking about the inner workings of quarkus:dev. Plus a nice surprise just implemented. Next Episode On Monday May 18th 15:00 CEST / 18:30 IST / 09:00 EST we will do Quarkus Insights episode #3: Hibernate...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-2/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ideas on Quarkus command-mode, UI-based apps and releasing via Github Actions</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-command-mode-tools/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus is advertised as a cloud-native runtime for Microservices but the introduction of command-mode might have opened up new and interesting spaces where it could find adoption. In this blog post I will present a few ideas about the possible usage of command-mode in Quarkus that you might find useful...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-command-mode-tools/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Insights #1: Tests</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-1/
            </link>
            <description>
                Monday we went live with Quarkus Insights #1: Testing with Georgios showing and talking about all things Testing. Especially showing the new Mockito integration and examples of TestContainer usage. The code he shows are at https://github.com/geoand/quarkus-test-demo and below are a transcript (Thanks Markus!). Next Episode On Tusday May 12th 11:15...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights-1/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #6</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-6/
            </link>
            <description>
                Welcome to #6, better late than never! Its been a busy time, with releases, Red Hat Summit and other virtual events. Noone stood still and this months list of news shows things are moving fast. In addittion to the newsletter we started Quarkusio Insights Live which is a live video...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-6/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Sedona rewrites insurance premium actuarial engine using Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sedona-rewrites-insurance-premium/
            </link>
            <description>
                Sedona, founded in 1998 and headquartered in Paris, is a consulting and information technology services company with offices in 3 countries: France, Switzerland, and China. Sedona has 180 experts worldwide, with 40% of those based out of the Paris office. Sedona responded to a call for tenders (request for proposal)...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sedona-rewrites-insurance-premium/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.4.2.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-4-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.4.2.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.4.1.Final. What&#8217;s new? You can get the full changelog of 1.4.2.Final on GitHub. Come Join Us We value your feedback a lot so please report bugs, ask for improvements&#8230;&#8203; Let&#8217;s build...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-4-2-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Introducing Command Mode</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/introducing-command-mode/
            </link>
            <description>
                Ever wanted to use Quarkus awesome API&#8217;s and full feature set from a command line application ? Did you need to run a scheduled batch job now and then and not wanting to embed it into your main Quarkus built service ? Quarkus has thus far been used to write...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/introducing-command-mode/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Insights on Youtube Live</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights/
            </link>
            <description>
                Yesterday, Emmanuel Bernard and I kicked off Quarkus Insights #0: Inception. All based on this tweet where ~76% was up for us doing "something" in video/podcast&#8217;y style. It is going to be recorded live as part of our existing QuarkusIO channel. To be notified when new shows are planned and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/insights/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Mocking CDI beans in Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mocking/
            </link>
            <description>
                Testing Quarkus applications has been an important part of the Quarkus Developer Joy, which is why @QuarkusTest for testing JVM applications and @NativeTest for black-box testing of the native images have been part of Quarkus since the first release. A recurring request however amongst our community members has been to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mocking/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for Eclipse 4.15.0.Final release !</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/eclipse-quarkus-tools-4.15.0.Final/
            </link>
            <description>
                In a previous post, we announced the first version of Quarkus Tools for Eclipse. We&#8217;re now announcing a new version for Quarkus Tools for Eclipse, including better support for Eclipse Microprofile, Java 11 and enhancements to the wizard. Language support for Kubernetes, Openshift, S2i and Docker properties There is now...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/eclipse-quarkus-tools-4.15.0.Final/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
