<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 14:59:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.3.0.Final released - New class loader infrastructure, GraalVM 20 support and much much more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                In case you haven&#8217;t noticed, it has been a bit less than two months since our last major Quarkus release as we went through some extensive testing phases to validate our new class loader infrastructure. A big thanks to all the people who tested our Alphas/CRs and provided feedback. Two...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ennovative Solutions uses Quarkus with AWS Lambda to deliver a better customer experience with their new product PURQR</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/ennovativesolutions-uses-quarkus-with-aws-lambda/
            </link>
            <description>
                Ennovative Solutions is an IT Consulting and Services company out of Diepenbeek, Belgium. By working with many customers, including ones in retail, they identified that many of them were suffering low sales due to poor customer experience. As a result, in 2019, they created a new application called PURQR (Purchasing...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/ennovativesolutions-uses-quarkus-with-aws-lambda/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #5</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-5/
            </link>
            <description>
                Welcome to #5! This month a few blogs with everything from basic introduction, test-containers and a walkthrough on how to do multi-tenancy with Quarkus. Give it a go and if you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for future Quarkus Newsletter install the bookmarklet on your...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-5/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Qute - Why (Not Just) Yet Another Templating Engine</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute/
            </link>
            <description>
                Qute is an experimental feature. There is no guarantee of stability nor long term presence in the platform until the solution matures. An introduction guide and a more comprehensive reference guide are available. Let&#8217;s start with a very good question: "Why yet another templating engine?". There are plenty of templating...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.2.1.Final released - Bugfixes only</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-2-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released 1.2.1.Final which is a small iteration on top of 1.2.0.Final with only bugfixes and documentation fixes. This is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.2.0.Final. What&#8217;s new? Bugfixes and documentation improvements The most important issue we fixed is the regression in the MariaDB driver when building native...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-2-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Lufthansa Technik AVIATAR experiences significant cloud resources savings by moving to Kubernetes-native Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/aviatar-experiences-significant-savings/
            </link>
            <description>
                Lufthansa Technik, the world’s largest independent provider of airline maintenance, repair, and overhaul (MRO) services, runs a SaaS digital platform, called AVIATAR, for the aviation industry. This platform helps airlines avoid delays and cancellations by using data to better organize and schedule maintenance. The company built and operated AVIATAR using...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/aviatar-experiences-significant-savings/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Suomen Asiakastieto Oy chooses Quarkus for their microservices development</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/asiakastieto-chooses-quarkus-for-microservices/
            </link>
            <description>
                Based in Helsinki, Finland, The Asiakastieto Group is a leading provider of innovative, digital business and consumer information services in the Nordic region. In the banking, financial services, and retail industries, Asiakastieto’s products and services support risk management, finance and business administration, credit or loan-related decision-making, sales and marketing. When...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/asiakastieto-chooses-quarkus-for-microservices/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Introducing 10 new features in Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.3.0</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.3.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.3.0 has been released on the VS Code Marketplace , the first release of the year. Alongside various bug fixes, this release focused on introducing VS Code support that accompanies new Quarkus features like application.yaml support, server-side templating support and the Quarkus 1.2 kebab-case...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.3.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.2.0.Final released - GraalVM 19.3.1 support, Metrics, Cache extension, and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-2-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It has been one month since your last Quarkus fix and you are getting used to our frequent releases so here comes 1.2.0.Final. We have been hard at work to bring a lot of exciting new features: GraalVM 19.3.1 support is finally there, we added a new Cache extension to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-2-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus wins DEVIES award</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-wins-devies-award/
            </link>
            <description>
                On January 22, 2020, we were informed that Quarkus had won the DeveloperWeek DEVIES Awards in the category of Best Innovation in: Code Frameworks/Libraries. As a Kubernetes-native Java stack, Quarkus represents a fundamental shift in modern application development that makes Java a great fit for cloud-native application architectures, such as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-wins-devies-award/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
