<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 22:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code - 1.4.0 release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.4.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.4.0 has been released on the VS Code Marketplace. vscode-quarkus 1.4.0 fixes several bugs, including some performance issues, but the highlights of this release revolve around bringing support for multiple MicroProfile modules (Fault Tolerance, Health, LRA, Metrics, Open API, Open Tracing, Rest Client), in...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.4.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Why did Payair Technologies switch to Quarkus?</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-did-payair-technologies-switch-to-quarkus/
            </link>
            <description>
                Developing cloud-ready solutions has become an industry standard, especially in the enterprise world. Sooner or later your application has to face the problem of poor horizontal scalability or high memory usage and we all know it is better to be prepared. We understand this at Payair as well. When we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-did-payair-technologies-switch-to-quarkus/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.3.2.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released 1.3.2.Final today with bugfixes and documentation improvements. This is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.3.0.Final or 1.3.1.Final. It is a very recommended upgrade if you are using Hibernate ORM. What&#8217;s new? Bugfixes We fixed a couple of regressions introduced recently in the Hibernate ORM extension. We...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-2-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Eclipse got Quarkused !</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/eclipse-got-quarkused/
            </link>
            <description>
                You have probably already heard about tooling for Microsoft VSCode or JetBrains IntelliJ. Last week the first version of Quarkus Tools for Eclipse was released. It&#8217;s free and open source and we encourage you to use it. Let&#8217;s see how you can get it and play with the features. Installation...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/eclipse-got-quarkused/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.3.1.Final released - Bugfixes, JDK 11 by default</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released 1.3.1.Final which is a bugfix version on top of 1.3.0.Final. This version contains bugfixes and documentation improvements and makes Java 11 our default target for newly generated projects. This is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.3.0.Final. What&#8217;s new? Java 11 by default This was an oversight...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.3 and Eclipse MicroProfile 3.3</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-eclipse-microprofile-3-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                With the announcement that Quarkus 1.3 is now available, we’re pleased to additionally announce that Quarkus 1.3 passes the TCKs of all Eclipse MicroProfile 3.3 specifications. MicroProfile 3.3 includes the following specification updates: Config 1.4 Fault Tolerance 2.1 Health 2.2 Metrics 2.3 REST Client 1.4 Config The Config update includes...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-eclipse-microprofile-3-3/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.3.0.Final released - New class loader infrastructure, GraalVM 20 support and much much more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                In case you haven&#8217;t noticed, it has been a bit less than two months since our last major Quarkus release as we went through some extensive testing phases to validate our new class loader infrastructure. A big thanks to all the people who tested our Alphas/CRs and provided feedback. Two...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-3-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ennovative Solutions uses Quarkus with AWS Lambda to deliver a better customer experience with their new product PURQR</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/ennovativesolutions-uses-quarkus-with-aws-lambda/
            </link>
            <description>
                Ennovative Solutions is an IT Consulting and Services company out of Diepenbeek, Belgium. By working with many customers, including ones in retail, they identified that many of them were suffering low sales due to poor customer experience. As a result, in 2019, they created a new application called PURQR (Purchasing...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/ennovativesolutions-uses-quarkus-with-aws-lambda/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #5</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-5/
            </link>
            <description>
                Welcome to #5! This month a few blogs with everything from basic introduction, test-containers and a walkthrough on how to do multi-tenancy with Quarkus. Give it a go and if you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for future Quarkus Newsletter install the bookmarklet on your...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-5/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Qute - Why (Not Just) Yet Another Templating Engine</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute/
            </link>
            <description>
                Qute is an experimental feature. There is no guarantee of stability nor long term presence in the platform until the solution matures. An introduction guide and a more comprehensive reference guide are available. Let&#8217;s start with a very good question: "Why yet another templating engine?". There are plenty of templating...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
