<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 16:47:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus wins DEVIES award</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-wins-devies-award/
            </link>
            <description>
                On January 22, 2020, we were informed that Quarkus had won the DeveloperWeek DEVIES Awards in the category of Best Innovation in: Code Frameworks/Libraries. As a Kubernetes-native Java stack, Quarkus represents a fundamental shift in modern application development that makes Java a great fit for cloud-native application architectures, such as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-wins-devies-award/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>New fault tolerance implementation in Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-fault-tolerance-4-0/
            </link>
            <description>
                Since its first release, Quarkus lets you create resilient applications with MicroProfile Fault Tolerance. It uses SmallRye Fault Tolerance to provide this functionality. At the time SmallRye Fault Tolerance was born, Hystrix was still a thing and was chosen to be the core of the implementation. The choice turned out...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-fault-tolerance-4-0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus is Eclipse MicroProfile 3.2 compatible!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-eclipse-microprofile-3-2-compatible/
            </link>
            <description>
                With the announcement that Quarkus 1.1 was available in December 2019, and after a tremendous effort from all the contributors and community, we’re excited to announce that Quarkus 1.1 is Eclipse MicroProfile 3.2 compatible! MicroProfile 3.2 was released November 2019, bringing updates to the Metrics and Health specifications, but what...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-eclipse-microprofile-3-2-compatible/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus support in IDE's</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/march-of-ides/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus is still young and thus it might come as a surprise to some there are actually already a good amount of Quarkus support in most of the various IDE&#8217;s. Its important to realize that Quarkus is using mainly standard technology and API thus no special IDE tooling is required...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/march-of-ides/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Sentry Error Tracker - A guardian of your Quarkus application</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sentry-the-guardian-of-your-quarkus-app/
            </link>
            <description>
                If like me you have met Quarkus and fell in love, you started implementing your backend and you started to feel so light and quick, click clack, whoot whoot&#8230;&#8203; in a woosh, your lightning fast native container is ready to be sent on your brand new Kubernetes cluster 🤙 This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sentry-the-guardian-of-your-quarkus-app/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #4</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-4/
            </link>
            <description>
                For the first Quarkus Newsletter of 2020 we got quite a nice selection! People trying out the new experimental template engine Qute for Quarkus, migration of existing apps, framework comparisons, MapStruct and an excellent video on deploying Quarkus in the real-world. Give it a go and if you feel something...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-4/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.1.1.Final released - Bugfixes only</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released 1.1.1.Final to push a series of bugfixes and documentation improvements early. We are still working hard on preparing our next big version, which will be 1.2, released in late January. This is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.1.0.Final. What&#8217;s new? Bugfixes and documentation improvements We introduced...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.1.0.Final released - Template engine, YAML configuration, and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Just in time for the holiday season, Quarkus 1.1.0.Final is here with all its extensions (Camel Quarkus included) ready for you. The inception of this version had a few twists and turns but that makes for a good story. It is packed with new features most notably the Qute template...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Delay in GraalVM 19.3 support - planned for Quarkus 1.2 - here is why</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-graalvm-19-2/
            </link>
            <description>
                One of the highly anticipated features of Quarkus 1.1.0.CR1 was the GraalVM 19.3 support. GraalVM 19.3 changes quite a lot of things (JDK 11 preview etc) and due to the deep integration between Quarkus and GraalVM, it was an all-or-nothing update for us as we couldn&#8217;t support both GraalVM 19.2...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-graalvm-19-2/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #3</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                The third Quarkus Newsletter is here to give you some reading material for the last weeks left of good old 2019. This time around we got the very first book on Quarkus! Give it a go and if you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-3/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
