<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 10:39:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus support in IDE's</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/march-of-ides/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus is still young and thus it might come as a surprise to some there are actually already a good amount of Quarkus support in most of the various IDE&#8217;s. Its important to realize that Quarkus is using mainly standard technology and API thus no special IDE tooling is required...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/march-of-ides/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Sentry Error Tracker - A guardian of your Quarkus application</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sentry-the-guardian-of-your-quarkus-app/
            </link>
            <description>
                If like me you have met Quarkus and fell in love, you started implementing your backend and you started to feel so light and quick, click clack, whoot whoot&#8230;&#8203; in a woosh, your lightning fast native container is ready to be sent on your brand new Kubernetes cluster 🤙 This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sentry-the-guardian-of-your-quarkus-app/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #4</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-4/
            </link>
            <description>
                For the first Quarkus Newsletter of 2020 we got quite a nice selection! People trying out the new experimental template engine Qute for Quarkus, migration of existing apps, framework comparisons, MapStruct and an excellent video on deploying Quarkus in the real-world. Give it a go and if you feel something...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-4/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.1.1.Final released - Bugfixes only</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released 1.1.1.Final to push a series of bugfixes and documentation improvements early. We are still working hard on preparing our next big version, which will be 1.2, released in late January. This is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.1.0.Final. What&#8217;s new? Bugfixes and documentation improvements We introduced...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.1.0.Final released - Template engine, YAML configuration, and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Just in time for the holiday season, Quarkus 1.1.0.Final is here with all its extensions (Camel Quarkus included) ready for you. The inception of this version had a few twists and turns but that makes for a good story. It is packed with new features most notably the Qute template...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Delay in GraalVM 19.3 support - planned for Quarkus 1.2 - here is why</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-graalvm-19-2/
            </link>
            <description>
                One of the highly anticipated features of Quarkus 1.1.0.CR1 was the GraalVM 19.3 support. GraalVM 19.3 changes quite a lot of things (JDK 11 preview etc) and due to the deep integration between Quarkus and GraalVM, it was an all-or-nothing update for us as we couldn&#8217;t support both GraalVM 19.2...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-graalvm-19-2/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #3</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                The third Quarkus Newsletter is here to give you some reading material for the last weeks left of good old 2019. This time around we got the very first book on Quarkus! Give it a go and if you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-3/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>For fast innovation and to stay ahead of the competition, Talkdesk chooses Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/talkdesk-chooses-quarkus-for-fast-innovation/
            </link>
            <description>
                Talkdesk, founded in 2011, is a fast growing company with a cloud Contact Center as a service (CCaaS) solution featuring increased productivity, higher cost savings and better customer experience. Their platform includes voice solutions, digital channels, workforce engagement management, reporting and analytics, AI and automation, and integrations to third-party software,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/talkdesk-chooses-quarkus-for-fast-innovation/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.0.1.Final released - Important security fix</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released 1.0.1.Final to fix an important security issue introduced in CR2 and still present in 1.0.0.Final. Please upgrade to this version as soon as possible if you are using our security layer. What&#8217;s new? Security issue fix If you are using our security annotations (e.g. @RolesAllowed) and also...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.0.0.Final bits are here</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-0-Final-bits-are-here/
            </link>
            <description>
                After two release candidates, we are happy to announce that Quarkus 1.0.0.Final has been released. You can read Quarkus 1.0&#8217;s announcement here. We have now our heads towards the future. Many thanks to all the communities we rely on and interact with to provide the Quarkus ecosystem: Netty, Vert.x, RESTEasy,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-0-Final-bits-are-here/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
