<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 07:53:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.1.0.Final released - Template engine, YAML configuration, and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Just in time for the holiday season, Quarkus 1.1.0.Final is here with all its extensions (Camel Quarkus included) ready for you. The inception of this version had a few twists and turns but that makes for a good story. It is packed with new features most notably the Qute template...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-1-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Delay in GraalVM 19.3 support - planned for Quarkus 1.2 - here is why</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-graalvm-19-2/
            </link>
            <description>
                One of the highly anticipated features of Quarkus 1.1.0.CR1 was the GraalVM 19.3 support. GraalVM 19.3 changes quite a lot of things (JDK 11 preview etc) and due to the deep integration between Quarkus and GraalVM, it was an all-or-nothing update for us as we couldn&#8217;t support both GraalVM 19.2...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/why-graalvm-19-2/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #3</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                The third Quarkus Newsletter is here to give you some reading material for the last weeks left of good old 2019. This time around we got the very first book on Quarkus! Give it a go and if you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-3/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>For fast innovation and to stay ahead of the competition, Talkdesk chooses Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/talkdesk-chooses-quarkus-for-fast-innovation/
            </link>
            <description>
                Talkdesk, founded in 2011, is a fast growing company with a cloud Contact Center as a service (CCaaS) solution featuring increased productivity, higher cost savings and better customer experience. Their platform includes voice solutions, digital channels, workforce engagement management, reporting and analytics, AI and automation, and integrations to third-party software,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/talkdesk-chooses-quarkus-for-fast-innovation/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.0.1.Final released - Important security fix</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released 1.0.1.Final to fix an important security issue introduced in CR2 and still present in 1.0.0.Final. Please upgrade to this version as soon as possible if you are using our security layer. What&#8217;s new? Security issue fix If you are using our security annotations (e.g. @RolesAllowed) and also...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.0.0.Final bits are here</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-0-Final-bits-are-here/
            </link>
            <description>
                After two release candidates, we are happy to announce that Quarkus 1.0.0.Final has been released. You can read Quarkus 1.0&#8217;s announcement here. We have now our heads towards the future. Many thanks to all the communities we rely on and interact with to provide the Quarkus ecosystem: Netty, Vert.x, RESTEasy,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-0-Final-bits-are-here/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code - 1.2.0 release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.2.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are proud to present the new release of Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code, providing a feature-rich development experience in VS Code for Quarkus application development. This release focused on introducing tooling support for Gradle projects, as well as adding new application.properties language features. Watch a demo of the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.2.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.0.0.CR2 released - Last stop before Final</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-0-CR2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We have been busy bees fixing the reported issues, improving the documentation and the global developer experience. And we felt that a second candidate release was in order due to some of the changes we made. Please, update your applications as soon as possible and, if you encounter any issues,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-0-0-CR2-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #2</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-2/
            </link>
            <description>
                Welcome to the second episode of the Quarkus Newsletter. This is where we&#8217;ll post about new found publications related to Quarkus. If you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for future Quarkus Newsletter posts please open an issue with a short description and a url. This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-2/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vodafone Greece replaces Spring Boot with Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vodafone-greece-replaces-spring-boot/
            </link>
            <description>
                Vodafone Greece is the second largest telecommunications company in Greece providing fixed and wireless phone service to over 6M subscribers. Vodafone Greece runs many applications on-premise and on the cloud so cloud resource consumption costs are extremely important to them. One component of their architecture is the Digital eXperience Layer...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vodafone-greece-replaces-spring-boot/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
