<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:36:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.6.1.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-6-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.6.1.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.6.0.Final. What&#8217;s new? Apart from bugfixes and usability improvements, Quarkus 1.6.1.Final introduces one behavior change: when building a native executable with GraalVM, the file.encoding is now set to UTF-8. It won&#8217;t...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-6-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus now supports test profiles</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-test-profiles/
            </link>
            <description>
                With the release of Quarkus 1.6 Quarkus now supports test profiles, allowing you to easily test multiple different configurations inside the same module. This post outlines what test profiles are and how you can use them. Recap on how @QuarkusTest works Before we talk about test profiles let&#8217;s talk briefly...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-test-profiles/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>A Shot of Quarkus with a Cassandra Chaser: Time for Faster Microservices</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-cassandra-extension-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                With the new Quarkus extension for Apache Cassandra® released in Quarkus 1.6, all it takes is a few lines of code to connect to and access your data stored in Cassandra and you get all of the benefits of Quarkus (fast-startup, low resource utilization, reactive programming). To enable the extension,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-cassandra-extension-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.6 released - AppCDS, Google Cloud Functions, GraalVM 20.1.0 and more...</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-6-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Summer is here and we are still hard at work improving Quarkus at a rapid pace. Of course, we improved our existing features, our documentation and fixed bugs but we also delivered some very interesting new features: Integrated generation of AppCDS archives to improve startup time in JVM mode Support...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-6-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #7</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-7/
            </link>
            <description>
                Welcome to Quarkus Newletter #7, this time with a record number of links to Quarkus related articles/videos/etc. all found online for you to explore. For the news below - give it a read and if you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for future Quarkus Newsletter...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-7/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>gRPC with Quarkus!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-grpc/
            </link>
            <description>
                In Quarkus 1.5, we shipped the first version of the gRPC Quarkus extension. If you are not familiar with gRPC, it&#8217;s a highly efficient Remote Procedure Call mechanism relying on HTTP/2 and Protobuf. You can implement and consume gRPC services from any language such as Go, JavaScript, Python, and Java....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-grpc/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.0.0 release !</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.0.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.0.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release brings enhanced code completion and syntax validation for application.properties and better support for Microprofile in Java files. It is not based anymore on the LSP Support plugin in order to increase stability. In order...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.0.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Supersonic Subatomic GraphQL</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/supersonic-subatomic-graphql/
            </link>
            <description>
                MicroProfile GraphQL is now included in the just released version 1.5.0 of Quarkus. What is GraphQL? "GraphQL is an open-source data query and manipulation language for APIs, and a runtime for fulfilling queries with existing data. GraphQL interprets strings from the client, and returns data in an understandable, predictable, pre-defined...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/supersonic-subatomic-graphql/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.5.2.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.5.2.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.5.0.Final or 1.5.1.Final. What&#8217;s new? We fixed two important regressions: The IDE launcher is back on track. In 1.5, we tweaked how the Hibernate ORM Panache enhancement works and that might...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-5-2-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Global Hackathon</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-hackathon-announcement/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Quarkus community is excited to announce the Supersonic, Subatomic Java Hackathon for developers to create Kubernetes-native applications for a chance to win $30,000 in prizes. This hackathon is a great opportunity to learn about the future of cloud-native Java development and showcase your coding skills. The Quarkus community and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-hackathon-announcement/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
