<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 09:34:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Lufthansa Technik AVIATAR experiences significant cloud resources savings by moving to Kubernetes-native Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/aviatar-experiences-significant-savings/
            </link>
            <description>
                Lufthansa Technik, the world’s largest independent provider of airline maintenance, repair, and overhaul (MRO) services, runs a SaaS digital platform, called AVIATAR, for the aviation industry. This platform helps airlines avoid delays and cancellations by using data to better organize and schedule maintenance. The company built and operated AVIATAR using...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/aviatar-experiences-significant-savings/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Suomen Asiakastieto Oy chooses Quarkus for their microservices development</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/asiakastieto-chooses-quarkus-for-microservices/
            </link>
            <description>
                Based in Helsinki, Finland, The Asiakastieto Group is a leading provider of innovative, digital business and consumer information services in the Nordic region. In the banking, financial services, and retail industries, Asiakastieto’s products and services support risk management, finance and business administration, credit or loan-related decision-making, sales and marketing. When...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/asiakastieto-chooses-quarkus-for-microservices/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Introducing 10 new features in Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.3.0</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.3.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.3.0 has been released on the VS Code Marketplace , the first release of the year. Alongside various bug fixes, this release focused on introducing VS Code support that accompanies new Quarkus features like application.yaml support, server-side templating support and the Quarkus 1.2 kebab-case...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.3.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.2.0.Final released - GraalVM 19.3.1 support, Metrics, Cache extension, and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-2-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It has been one month since your last Quarkus fix and you are getting used to our frequent releases so here comes 1.2.0.Final. We have been hard at work to bring a lot of exciting new features: GraalVM 19.3.1 support is finally there, we added a new Cache extension to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-2-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus wins DEVIES award</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-wins-devies-award/
            </link>
            <description>
                On January 22, 2020, we were informed that Quarkus had won the DeveloperWeek DEVIES Awards in the category of Best Innovation in: Code Frameworks/Libraries. As a Kubernetes-native Java stack, Quarkus represents a fundamental shift in modern application development that makes Java a great fit for cloud-native application architectures, such as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-wins-devies-award/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>New fault tolerance implementation in Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-fault-tolerance-4-0/
            </link>
            <description>
                Since its first release, Quarkus lets you create resilient applications with MicroProfile Fault Tolerance. It uses SmallRye Fault Tolerance to provide this functionality. At the time SmallRye Fault Tolerance was born, Hystrix was still a thing and was chosen to be the core of the implementation. The choice turned out...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-fault-tolerance-4-0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus is Eclipse MicroProfile 3.2 compatible!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-eclipse-microprofile-3-2-compatible/
            </link>
            <description>
                With the announcement that Quarkus 1.1 was available in December 2019, and after a tremendous effort from all the contributors and community, we’re excited to announce that Quarkus 1.1 is Eclipse MicroProfile 3.2 compatible! MicroProfile 3.2 was released November 2019, bringing updates to the Metrics and Health specifications, but what...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-eclipse-microprofile-3-2-compatible/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus support in IDE's</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/march-of-ides/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus is still young and thus it might come as a surprise to some there are actually already a good amount of Quarkus support in most of the various IDE&#8217;s. Its important to realize that Quarkus is using mainly standard technology and API thus no special IDE tooling is required...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/march-of-ides/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Sentry Error Tracker - A guardian of your Quarkus application</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sentry-the-guardian-of-your-quarkus-app/
            </link>
            <description>
                If like me you have met Quarkus and fell in love, you started implementing your backend and you started to feel so light and quick, click clack, whoot whoot&#8230;&#8203; in a woosh, your lightning fast native container is ready to be sent on your brand new Kubernetes cluster 🤙 This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/sentry-the-guardian-of-your-quarkus-app/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #4</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-4/
            </link>
            <description>
                For the first Quarkus Newsletter of 2020 we got quite a nice selection! People trying out the new experimental template engine Qute for Quarkus, migration of existing apps, framework comparisons, MapStruct and an excellent video on deploying Quarkus in the real-world. Give it a go and if you feel something...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-4/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
