<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 10:32:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vodafone Greece replaces Spring Boot with Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vodafone-greece-replaces-spring-boot/
            </link>
            <description>
                







Vodafone Greece is the second largest telecommunications company in Greece providing fixed and wireless phone service to over 6M subscribers.


Vodafone Greece runs many applications on-premise and on the cloud so cloud resource consumption costs are extremely important to them. One component of their architecture is the Digital eXperience Layer (DXL), a Kubernetes-based software, which...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vodafone-greece-replaces-spring-boot/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus for Spring Developers</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-for-spring-developers/
            </link>
            <description>
                
The arrival of Quarkus 1.0 brings an innovative platform for developing Linux container- and kubernetes-native Java microservices. Developers typically have to set aside their existing knowledge as they begin to evaluate new and innovative runtime frameworks. Quarkus is different because it was created by a collection of engineers with a deep expertise in a broad collection of Java technologie...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-for-spring-developers/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>GoWithFlow chooses Quarkus to deliver fast to production with minimal risk</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/gowithflow-chooses-quarkus-to-deliver-fast-to-production/
            </link>
            <description>
                







GoWithFlow, a recent startup based out of Portugal, a spin-off from CEiiA with Galp as a majority shareholder, provides integrated mobility solutions that can both provision end-to-end services to new mobility operators (eg. running a scooter-sharing network, managing an EV charging network, managing a fleet), but also gather data from other mobility operators, e.g.car-sharing operators...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/gowithflow-chooses-quarkus-to-deliver-fast-to-production/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Announcing Quarkus 1.0</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/announcing-quarkus-1-0/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Quarkus is an Open Source stack to write Java applications offering unparalleled startup time, memory footprint and developer experience. It offers familiar programming models and APIs (Hibernate, JAX-RS, Eclipse Vert.x, Apache Camel, Eclipse MicroProfile, Spring API compatibility and more).


Today marks a real milestone for the Quarkus community and the Java community at large. Quarkus 1.0 C...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/announcing-quarkus-1-0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.28.1 released - Some more bugfixes, help us squash 404s</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-28-1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
This release is a bugfix/usability improvements release so the upgrade from 0.27.0 should be safe.


One new item is that we now have a notion of platform to refer to a set of extensions in the Quarkus ecosystem. Details below on how to use/try it out.


What&#8217;s new?


New website theme

We just pushed a new theme for the website. We are still working on polishing it but, if you see somet...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-28-1-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code - 1.1.0 release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.1.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                
What’s new with Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code


The 1.1.0 release of Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code
offers more language features for the application.properties file and new additions to existing
features like validation and snippets support.


For a list of all changes, please refer to the changelog.




New features




Value type validation for application.properties


Go to de...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.1.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.27.0 released - More Amazon Lambda goodness</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-27-0-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Another week, another release, this time with a focus on Amazon Lambda, usability and bugfixes.









If you are generating native images, the recommended version of GraalVM is now 19.2.1 so please upgrade!






What&#8217;s new?


Amazon Lambda

We were hard at work to get the Amazon Lambda features on par with the Azure Functions ones. You can now use traditional Lambdas or RESTEasy/JAX-...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-27-0-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.26.1 released - Stabilizing things and adding Vault support</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-26-1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Keeping the rapid pace of one release per week, here comes Quarkus 0.26.1.


Thanks a lot to the community at large for the useful bug reports, that helps a lot in stabilizing the new HTTP and security layers. Keep them coming.


Apart from bugfixes, the new big thing in 0.26.1 is an extension adding support for HashiCorp Vault.









The recommended version of GraalVM is still 19.2.0.1 as ...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-26-1-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.25.0 released - Security layer updated</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-25.0-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Just a few days after 0.24.0, and to stay in line with our planning, we release 0.25.0.


This release fixes a couple of issues, mostly related to the new HTTP layer and brings some updates to the currently being rewritten security layer.


What&#8217;s new?


Security layer changes

HTTP based permissions can now be defined in the application.properties.


This new feature is fully documented...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-0-25.0-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus on JBoss Asylum Podcast</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-on-jboss-asylum-podcast/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Last week in a hotel room in Boston I managed to get Jason, Emmanuel and Bill from the Quarkus team to sit down and record episode #46 of JBoss Asylum.


The episode is called "Quarkus to the bones" where we all four go into the details on the why and how on how Quarkus was created and what it is good for - all while having a bit of fun.


The episode is posted on JBoss Community Asylum and al...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-on-jboss-asylum-podcast/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
