<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io/</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 17:18:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.23.2 released - Back on track</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-23-2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Last week, we released Quarkus 0.23.1 which paved the way towards our new Vert.x based HTTP layer and brought a lot of new features (see the original announcement post for all the details).
We discovered a memory usage regression shortly after the release: it was not a memory leak or anything that bad but an increased memory usage due to Netty getting a bit too comfortable.


Today, we release...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-23-2-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #1</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-newsletter-1/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Welcome to the first episode of the Quarkus Newsletter. This is where we&#8217;ll post about new found publications related to Quarkus.


If you feel something is missing or have an article coming out for future Quarkus Newsletter posts please open an issue with a short description and a url.


In this first edition I&#8217;ve gathered list of interesting publications since the launch of Quark...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-newsletter-1/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.23.1 released - Paving the way to our new HTTP layer</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-23-1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                







DO NOT USE 0.23.1 - PLEASE USE 0.23.2.


We found a major memory regression in 0.23.1, we urge you to not use it and use 0.23.2 instead.






We just released Quarkus 0.23.1.
This version is an important milestone for us as it materializes one of our major objectives: relying on Vert.x for our entire HTTP layer.
It also comes with a lot of improvements and bugfixes contributed by our v...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-23-1-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus developer joy for VS Code</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-developer-joy-for-vs-code/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Earlier this year, we have been introduced to Quarkus, the next-generation, container-first framework for Java applications.
As expected, such new frameworks and technologies make way for new developer tools focused on making
the development experience even better.
The recent Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code release
aims to do just that,
by bringing features specific to Quarkus project dev...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-developer-joy-for-vs-code/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.22.0 released</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-22-0-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
We just released Quarkus 0.22.0 including an improved Spring API support.


We also officially launch code.quarkus.io: it has never been easier to create a Quarkus application.


What&#8217;s new?


Improved Spring API support

Quarkus has had a Quarkus Extension for Spring Dependency Injection API since its initial release. The plan has always been to extend Spring API support and executing o...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-22-0-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.21.2 released</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-21-2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
We just released Quarkus 0.21.2.


What&#8217;s new?


This release is all about fixing bugs, usability and documentation issues. We are still working on our next big release which will be 0.22.0.


You can find the full changelog of 0.21.2 on GitHub.


We have a lot of interesting things in the works so stay tuned.




Contributors


Quarkus has now 142 contributors.
Many many thanks to each ...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-21-2-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.21.1 released</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-21-1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
We just released Quarkus 0.21.1.


As for 0.20.0, to build native executables, you will need GraalVM 19.1.1.


What&#8217;s new?


This release is mostly about fixing bugs and usability issues. The Kafka Streams and Apache Tika extensions got their usability greatly improved for instance.


You can find the full changelog of 0.21.0 and the few additional issues we fixed in 0.21.1 on GitHub.


...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-21-1-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Tips to use Hibernate ORM with Quarkus profiles and live coding mode</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/hibernate-orm-config-profiles/
            </link>
            <description>
                
Quarkus live coding (aka dev mode) is really useful for applications that mix front end or services and database access.
There are a few common approaches to make the best of it.


The first choice is to use quarkus.hibernate-orm.database.generation=drop-and-create in conjunction with import.sql.
That way for every change to your app and in particular to your entities, the database schema will...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/hibernate-orm-config-profiles/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using CircleCI to Build a Native Quarkus Application</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-app-circleci-build/
            </link>
            <description>
                


An important part of any software project, Quarkus applications included, is continuous integration. A popular
tool in the CI space is CircleCI, especially with open source projects. There is lots
of documentation out there about how to configure CircleCI for a standard Maven project. However, building a native
Quarkus executable requires one or two extra steps. This blog post describes how ...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-app-circleci-build/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 0.20.0 released</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-20-0-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                
We just released Quarkus 0.20.0.









If you use Quarkus with GraalVM to build native executables, Quarkus 0.20.0 now requires GraalVM 19.1.1 so please upgrade your GraalVM installation.






What&#8217;s new?


Here are the main highlights of this release: Jackson extensions, OAuth2 extension, Camel extensions moved outside the Quarkus tree, a new MicroProfile REST Client implementation,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io//blog/quarkus-0-20-0-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
